hibiki-an.com 2019-05-24

# Privacy Notice - JAPANESE GREEN TEA | HIBIKI-AN

We collect your personal information in order to provide and continually improve our products and services.

Here are the types of information we gather:

  * Information You Give Us: we receive and store any information you provide in relation to Hibiki-an Services. Click [here](https://www.hibiki-an.com/contents.php/cnID/97#privacynotice020801) to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our Hibiki-an Services. 
  * Automatic Information: we automatically receive and store certain types of information when you use Hibiki-an Services, such as information about your use, including your interaction with content and services available through Hibiki-an Services. Like many websites, we use cookies and other unique identifiers and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser or device accesses Hibiki-an Services and other content served by or on behalf of Hibiki-an on other websites. Click [here](https://www.hibiki-an.com/contents.php/cnID/97#privacynotice020802) to see examples of what we collect. 

We process your personal information to operate, provide, and improve the Hibiki-an Services that we offer our customers. These purposes include: 

  * Purchase and delivery of products and services. We use your personal information to take and handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, and communicate with you about orders, products and services, and promotional offers. 
  * Provide, troubleshoot, and improve Hibiki-an Services. We use your personal information to provide functionality, analyse performance, fix errors, and improve usability and effectiveness of the Hibiki-an Services. 
  * Comply with legal obligations. In certain cases, we have a legal obligation to collect and process your personal information. For instance, we collect from sellers information regarding place of establishment and bank account information for identity verification and other purposes. 
  * Communicate with you. We use your personal information to communicate with you in relation to Hibiki-an Services via different channels (e.g., by phone, email, chat). 
  * Fraud Prevention and Credit Risks. We process personal information to prevent and detect fraud and abuse in order to protect the security of our customers, Hibiki-an, and others. We may also use scoring methods to assess and manage credit risks. 

### What About Cookies?

##### What About Cookies?

To enable our systems to recognise your browser or device and to provide Hibiki-an Services to you, we use cookies. For more information about cookies and how we use them, please read our [Cookies Notice.](https://www.hibiki-an.com/contents.php/cnID/97#privacynotice03)

### Does Hibiki-an Share Your Personal Information?

##### Does Hibiki-an Share Your Personal Information?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling our customers' personal information to others. Hibiki-an shares customers' information only as described below controls that are either subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. 

  * Third Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders for products or services, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing payments, transmitting content, scoring credit risk, and providing customer service. These third-party service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Notice and as permitted by applicable data protection laws. 
  * Protection of Hibiki-an and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of Hibiki-an, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 
  * Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when personal information about you might be shared with third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

Transfers out of the European Economic Area. Whenever we transfer personal information to countries outside of the European Economic Area in the course of sharing information as set out above, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Notice and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection. 

### How Secure is Information About Me?

##### How Secure is Information About Me?

We design our systems with your security and privacy in mind.

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 
  * Our checkout process follows the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) when handling credit card data. 
  * We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personal customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computers, devices, and applications. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer. For more information on how to sign off. 

### What Information Can I Access?

##### What Information Can I Access?

You can access your information, including your name, address, payment options, profile information, Prime membership, household settings, and purchase history in the "My Account" section of the website. 

### Are Children Allowed to Use Hibiki-an Services?

##### Are Children Allowed to Use Hibiki-an Services?

Hibiki-an doesn't sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you're under 18, you may use Hibiki-an Services only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

##### How Long Do We Keep Your Personal Information?

We keep your personal information to enable your continued use of Hibiki-an Services, for as long as it is required in order to fulfil the relevant purposes described in this Privacy Notice, as may be required by law such as for tax and accounting purposes, or as otherwise communicated to you. For example, we retain your transaction history so that you can review past purchases (and repeat orders if desired) and what addresses you have shipped orders to, and to improve the relevancy of products and content we recommend. 

### Contacts, Notices & Revisions

##### Contacts, Notices & Revisions

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Notice will change also. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

### Examples of Information Collected

##### Examples of Information Collected

Information You Give Us When You Use Hibiki-an Services

You provide information to us when you: 

  * search for products or services; 
  * place an order through Hibiki-an Services; 
  * provide information in My Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address or mobile number when shopping with us); 
  * communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; 

As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as: your name; address and phone number; your age; your location information; e-mail addresses of your friends and other people; content of reviews and e-mails to us; information and documents regarding identity and standing; corporate and financial information; and device log files and configurations, including Wi-Fi credentials. 

Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyse include: 

  * the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; 
  * login; e-mail address; password; 
  * the location of your device or computer; 
  * the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our website (including date and time); cookie number; products and/ or content you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), 

We may also use device identifiers, cookies, and other technologies on devices, applications and our web pages to collect browsing, usage or other technical information for fraud prevention purposes. 

Information You Can Access

Examples of information you can access through Hibiki-an Services include: 

  * status of recent orders (including subscriptions); 
  * your complete order history; 
  * personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password and address book; 
  * recommendations and the products you recently viewed that are the basis for recommendations (including Recommended for You and Improve Your Recommendations); 
  * shopping lists and gift registries (including Wish Lists); 
  * Your Profile (including your product Reviews, Recommendations, Reminders and personal profile). 

We use cookies and other technologies (collectively, "cookies") to recognise your browser or device, learn more about your interests, and provide you with essential features and services and for additional purposes, including: 

  * Recognising you when you sign-in to use our services. 
  * This allows us to provide you with product recommendations, and provide customised features and services. 
  * Keeping track of items stored in your shopping basket. 
  * Conducting research and diagnostics to improve Hibiki-an's content, products, and services. 
  * Preventing fraudulent activity. 
  * Improving security. 
  * Reporting. This allows us to measure and analyse the performance of our services. 

Hibiki-an cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Hibiki-an's essential features. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Basket, proceed to Checkout, or use any Hibiki-an products and services that require you to sign in. 

You can manage browser cookies through your browser settings. The 'Help' feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, how to disable cookies, and when cookies will expire. If you disable all cookies on your browser, we will not transfer cookies to your browser. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some features and services may not work.
